Now we're ready to go ahead and give our best at the tryout.
Now you're usually only going to be in the room for about five minutes so you have to make sure to give it your all.
Once you're ready to go in you'll be given a number by the judges.
You need to make sure you have this number tightly secured, it also needs to be visible.
Safety pins are an OK way to get it on.
So it tape.
You just don't want it to fall off, because this is how the judges are going to be able to give you your score.
You're usually going to be put in a group of about three girls.
You're going to do the cheer together.
You're going to do your stunts together, jump separate and tumble separate.
Usually you're going to start out with the cheer.
When you go into the room, you need to be prepared to answer questions.
Things we talked about earlier, your coach may ask you, why are you here?
Why do want to cheer?
You need to be confident.
You need to be able to deliver your answer.
You also just need to make sure that you're friendly because you're going to be spending a lot of time with these coaches, these captains.
And you just want to be a person that other people want to be around.
You're also going to be an active role model for your school.
It's better to go ahead and show the coach that you can do them than not to try it at all.
So now that we've performed, we definitely want to say thank you on our way out, our time it up, and clear the floor for someone else's turn to go ahead.